freed the chilli maintain that
welcome back two wheeler car service centre
and after both I have just taken it because I am
admitted in the hospital so a lot more was happening
so I went so let's see
[Music]
I am absolutely
I said not be amazed slowly my
heart is beating
for ghee on the roads not your medium money
Vashishtha
now half heart melted sweet loving eyes
hello viewers looted the vegetables service
centre near me
running towards the problems saiya service
centre have asked
how much it is Bhaiya ji does
not have change I also do not have change if there is
solidarity on this issue then give it to him
it is okay I am feeling fine
[Music]
I am safe let's go inside this is the
regulatory service centre true till now we are looking
now we will go inside and give them the bill there is a
receiver he will give this inside the service centre
all the car service people standing there that
this is the bill I have given for
how much it was on
this occasion that it has
happened
yes I slept here all the bikes and scooters are
serviced here or mecca this is valley
city jama service centre  And I have
also taken insurance, so
I bought the car after getting it
serviced and then I gave it for the first service, so
I am taking it after getting it serviced, it cost
me more than 154 maunds because
I was in the hospital so I was able to go to get it
and there is a delay in front of the insurance, so I will
not come late in that, I have just made up
my mind to leave everyone and I was like a
courtier that I will take it, you know, mother's horse, you
just have to show it in front of your eyes,
this is the chart, by remote it, after that they
give a lot, so that too there and then there is nothing like that,
I said in my personal video that
I have to go to the office,
I had said that loot loot moments later,
so finally after how many days should I show you my car, it was
raining so it is wet, we were
standing for a while, it will
all be cleaned, we should get it
cleaned, and then you
see, it has happened, it is
everyone's, it is the Pune team, you
a subject has changed, do it, did you get
benefited, do it, that
19th, do it
to Ajay
and tell me or
not, should you start
applying 24
I will tell you one by one what changes have happened in the vehicle, this morning the
meter was changed and the entire front body has
changed and the mode has changed, in the morning the brake, mobile
and seat cover and there was a problem in one of them, that too the
complete care and the entire way of the light in the
front, you guys can see all these
changes
and tell me children tell me
mp3
[music] it
can come, get it done
soon the scooter has been serviced, it is
running very well, there is no problem,
earlier there was a lot of problem,
now it is running very well, so
I hope because like this video,
who like this video please like, subscribe
and share, thank you, know
Ajay Ko
Jhal